[music]
[音乐]
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; There's money falling from the sky.
天上掉钱了。
[music]
[音乐]
the Knicks won the finals has a story of
尼克斯队赢得总冠军时身在纽约市的每个人，都有一个关于尼克斯队赢得总冠军时
when they were in New York City when the
自己身在纽约市的故事
Knicks won the finals.
。
This is my story.
这是我的故事。   情况
Not going well. Still can't get it up.
不太妙。 还是勃不起来。
They they they can't seem to get the
他们似乎无法启动
game the live game up. My little girls
游戏，无法进行直播。 我的小女儿们
wanted to go to like a watch party, but
想去参加观影派对，但是
the watch parties are just they're too
观影派对太
chaotic.
混乱了。
So the wife and I thought why not throw
于是我和妻子想，何不自己举办一个
our own watch party. So I came to the
观影派对呢？ 于是我来到
studio, we got the projector, I got a
工作室，我们拿来了投影仪、
speaker, got the battery, and then we
扬声器和电池，然后我们
found a nice spot and we set things up.
找到一个好地方，把东西都布置好了。
This is what it looked like when we
这是我们刚
started. We found a nice spot on a
开始时的样子。 我们在一条汽车不能通行的街道上找到了一个好地方
street with where cars can't drive down,
，摆放了
three little kids and four chairs. One
三个小孩和四把椅子。 其中一把
of the chairs was for me.
椅子是给我的。
Important detail here. When I'm with my
这里有个重要的细节。 当我和
kids, I don't have cameras and stuff cuz
孩子们在一起时，我不会带相机之类的东西，因为
I like to be present with them. So this
我喜欢全心全意地陪伴他们。 所以，
whole night, like the greatest New York
就像纽约最棒的一个夜晚一样
City night, I didn't film anything. Like
，我整晚都没拍任何东西。 就像
I had a point and shoot, I got a couple
我用傻瓜相机拍的那样，我拍了一些
clips, but everything else is just like
视频片段，但其他的一切都和
photos and videos from my friends'
我朋友手机里的照片和视频一样
phones.
。
&gt;&gt; My video seeing Knicks win at the
我在观赛派对上拍到了尼克斯队赢球的视频
Oh my god.
我的天啊。
&gt;&gt; Almost immediately people started
几乎立刻就有人
joining our little projector party.
加入我们的小型投影仪派对。
Fantastic. But there were some technical
极好的。 但出现了一些技术
snafus. See, the projector didn't have a
故障。 你看，投影仪没有
Bluetooth, and then the speaker didn't
蓝牙功能，音箱也
have like cable in. So I had to connect
没有线缆接口。所以我只能把
the speaker to Candace's phone, stream
音箱连接到坎迪斯的手机上，再
it from Candace's phone to the speaker,
从坎迪斯的手机把声音传输到音箱，
and then line that up with the
最后再把音箱对准
projector, but we we got it to work.
投影仪，不过我们最终还是成功了。
It's working.
它奏效了。   是的
Yeah.
。
Working great.
效果很好。
Then I realized every time I looked over
然后我发现，每次我回头看时
my shoulder, the crowd had doubled.
，人群都增加了一倍。
&gt;&gt; That would have been fine. We're going
那样就没问题了。 我们将
to get a second look at
再次审视“
&gt;&gt; Like exponentially.
像指数级增长”这个概念。
Everyone was having just the greatest
每个人都玩得非常开心
time.
。   真
&gt;&gt; I can't believe you put this all
不敢相信你竟然把这些都整理出来了
together.
。
&gt;&gt; Towards the end of the third quarter,
第三节比赛快结束时，
the crowd had grown to like several
人群已经聚集了
hundred, [music] but
几百人，[音乐]但
I noticed something catastrophic.
我注意到了一些灾难性的事情。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; When we got there, the battery was at
当我们到达那里时，电池电量为
100%. That was at the beginning of the
100%。 那是在
second quarter. At this moment, there
第二季度初。 当时，
was 2 minutes and 25 seconds left in the
第三节还剩 2 分 25 秒
third quarter, and the battery was at
，电池电量为
22%.
22%。
So, in my head I did some quick battery
于是，我脑子里快速计算了一下电池
math.
电量。
With 2:25 left in the third quarter, the
第三节还剩 2 分 25 秒时，
battery is at 22%. So, if you have the
电池电量为 22%。 所以，如果你把
second quarter plus the third quarter
第二节加上第三节，再
minus the 2:25 left in that quarter, you
减去第三节剩下的 2 分 25 秒，你
get a total of 21 minutes and 35 seconds
总共会得到 21 分 35 秒的
of game [music] play watched. That
比赛[音乐]播放观看时间。 那
equals 1,295 seconds. 1,295 seconds
相当于 1295 秒。  1295 秒
equals 78% of the total battery life. T
相当于电池总寿命的 78%。  T
equals 1,295 over .78, which is about
等于 1,295 除以 0.78，约等于
1,660.26 [music]
1,660.26 [音乐]
seconds.
秒。
Divide that by 60 and get the total
将该值除以 60，即可得到
battery life between 27 minutes and
27 分钟到
[music] 40 seconds. Take 27 minutes and
[音乐] 40 秒之间的总电池续航时间。 用 27 分
40 seconds minus the battery life used,
40 秒减去已消耗的电池电量，还
you're left with 6 minutes and 5 [music]
剩下 6 分 5 秒（音乐播放时间），
seconds before the battery hits zero.
之后电池电量就会耗尽。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; Now, with 2:25 left in the third, 12
现在，第三节还剩 2 分 25 秒，
minutes in the fourth, [music] you have
第四节还剩 12 分钟，[音乐]
14 minutes and 25 seconds of game play
比赛还剩 14 分 25 秒
left. And you take that 14 minutes and
。 游戏还剩 14 分
25 seconds of game play left, you minus
25 秒，减去
the battery has left in it, and it means
电池剩余的 6 分 5 秒（音乐播放时间），这意味着
with 8 minutes and 20 seconds of game
游戏还剩 8 分 20 秒时
play left, the battery is dead. [music]
，电池就没电了。  [音乐]
Catastrophic.
灾难性的。
KNICKS IN 5.
尼克斯队五场取胜。
KNICKS IN 5. is when the magic that is
尼克斯队五场取胜。这是
the people of New York City came
纽约市民的魔力凝聚
together.
在一起的时刻。
First this dude sitting right behind me,
首先是坐在我身后的那个家伙，就是
that guy.
他。
He ran all the way back to his apartment
他一路跑回公寓，把
and grabbed every extension cord he had.
所有能找到的延长线都拿了出来。
We conjured up about 35 ft of
我们找来了大约 35 英尺长的
daisy-chained extension cord.
串联延长线。
Then I went and got my car, but NYPD
然后我去取车，但是纽约警察局
wouldn't let me get anywhere near a
不让我靠近那条
closed down street that had 300 people
有 300 人聚集的封闭街道
on it. I begged them.
。 我苦苦哀求他们。
Very precarious situation anyway, but I
情况本来就很危险，但我还是把
got my truck close enough to plug an
卡车开近了一些，把
extension cord into my truck
延长线插到卡车上，
and then run that from my truck back to
然后从卡车把延长线拉到
the projector.
投影仪那里。
But
但是，
in order to switch power from the
为了将电源从
battery to the extension cord, I had to
电池切换到延长线，我不得不
unplug it and undo all that stuff that I
拔掉电源插头，并撤销我一
set up at the beginning. I did that, the
开始设置的所有东西。 我照做了，
power worked.
电源恢复正常了。
But then nothing else worked.
但之后其他方法都无效了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; We were down for like 5 or 6 minutes.
我们倒下了大概 5 到 6 分钟。
[music] The crowd was getting tested.
[音乐] 人群正在接受检测。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I was able to get the audio back up cuz
我终于恢复了音频，因为
that was coming off of Kenneth's phone
那是从肯尼斯的手机里传出来的，
and I felt like that bought me a couple
我觉得这为我争取了
of minutes, but the pressure was on.
几分钟时间，但压力很大。
I was like covered in sweat. There was
我当时浑身都是汗。
like this huge dude next to me helping
旁边有个身材魁梧的家伙在帮
me, [music] but I There was a moment I
我，（音乐），但我一度以为这事
didn't think it was going to happen.
不会发生了。   情况
&gt;&gt; Not going well.
不太妙。
&gt;&gt; Then just like that, as if God himself,
然后，就像上帝亲自
Jalen Brunson reached down from the
从云端伸出手来
clouds and blessed us, it came back on
祝福我们一样，比赛
with 5 minutes left in the fourth
在第四节还剩 5 分钟时重新开始了
quarter.
。
&gt;&gt; Come on.
快点。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; 20 seconds left.
还剩20秒。
[cheering]
[欢呼]